Alex@Hey, I want to ask you all something.
Alex@Has anything strange happened to you recently?
@Yes. - Yes, yes, yes!
Victoria@I got stuck in the washing machine the other day.
@I was stuck for so long. - Me too.
Alex@Me too.
Victoria@And it felt like someone was groping me all over.
Victoria@Samantha, was it you?
Samantha@What does it have to do with me?
Samantha@How could it possibly be me?
Samantha@Come on!
Samantha@I like guys, you know.
Samantha@Were you having a wet dream or something?
Victoria@Your desires are so strong.
Victoria@I often hear moaning sounds, you know.
Megan@Don't fight.
Alex@Megan and I have been feeling something strange lately.
Alex@It's like we're constantly being watched.
Alex@It's creepy.
Megan@When I sleep, I feel really cold.
Megan@Then I realize my blanket isn't covering me properly.
Megan@It's like it's been lifted off.
Megan@And my Bebe keeps getting moved around.
Samantha@Bebe?
Alex@It's her bear.
Megan@It's not a bear.
Megan@Its name is just Bebe.
Alex@Bebe.
Grace@Um...
Grace@My necklace was thrown into the kitchen.
Megan@Necklace?
Samantha@What's a necklace compared to this?
Samantha@My massager was thrown around!
Victoria@You probably put it there yourself.
Samantha@How is that possible?
Samantha@I'm so particular about cleanliness and hygiene.
Alex@It doesn't seem that way.
Emily@Um...
Emily@My things have been moved around too.
Emily@Do you remember the day we moved in?
Emily@I bumped into a photo frame, right?
Megan@I remember.
Alex@That ugly guy.
Emily@The photo of that guy inside...
Emily@I feel like something's off about it.
Emily@I don't know if it's related to all of this.
Alex@Hey, that photo was in black and white.